She never accepted this reconciled position.
But despite the queen's sour notes, the time of freedom can begin.
During the time of freedom, we did not say "now we live in the time of freedom".
On the other hand, it was said that you lived in the freest constitution.
People were satisfied and said it could not have been better written by angels.
It was illegal to talk badly about the new form of government.
It is now super-famous Voltaire describes Sweden, little Sweden-
-like the freest country in the world.
The one who stood back for the country to be free - Ulrika Eleonora-
-Sit only one year on the throne.
Next to him, the queen has a man, her husband, Fredrik of Essen.
Here, they both keep on the helm as a parable of controlling Sweden.
After all, Fredriks and Ulrika Eleonora's plan was that they would cooperate.
However, this does not agree with this, and the Queen chooses to abdicate.
Fredrik becomes Fredrik I.
It is during his reign that royal name stamps are introduced.
There are stamps with the king's signature.
Documents can be signed by the king without being present.
The stamp has sometimes been seen as a metaphor for the entire freedom time.
The stamps are highlighted as symbols of how weak royal power has been.
But you needed the king's signature.
We say the kings were weak and powerless at that time.
But we compare with previous kings.
It is undoubtedly that they are the most powerful politicians at that time.
This is another of the most powerful politicians - Arvid Horn.
He is the office president-
-And leads the work of the Council, the government of the time, which now governs the country.
He wanted the kingdom to be restored.
Without war, one would rebuild the kingdom and gain financial stability.
Two political groups are emerging after headgear.
The hats and hats were the origin of what then becomes parties.
You can see them as two networks that mobilized for different polls.
Who was a bit unclear.
-How do the dawn democracy look like?
-Riksdag was a state of the stand.
So it was priests, citizens, farmers and nobility who had their own parliament.
Every stand has a vote, but it's not so democratic.
Many belong to no stand-
-And the stands represent different part of the population.
Each stand had its own room.
Delegations of noblemen went to the priests and shared them their decisions.
"Thanks so much," says the priests, and then they do the same in turn.
But outside these premises, people often stood waiting.
Where the farmer met, there was a staircase that was often full of people.
They stood listening to the decisions that were made.
The 18th century day is quite messy.
People are loud and sometimes unsuccessful.
Parliamentary representatives receive no salary, but may support themselves elsewhere.
Corruption was quite common.
That you received bribes or that you embezzled money from the Treasury.
It is easy to keep track of who is who in the Swedish position society.
They sit in different buildings.
But outside it becomes increasingly trickier.
It will be abundance regulations-
-which regulates who is allowed to use what types of goods.
To keep on the hierarchies, but also to promote Swedish goods.
If you are born in the peasantry, you must not by law carry silk.
People can be mistaken for your stand.
Citizens can be fined if they carry a guard.
Only the nobility must do that.
You are not allowed to dress over your stand.
Those who are at the bottom of the hierarchy come to trial for such crimes.
Especially maids.
And the fine is soaring.
Social mobility does not exist in the Swedish Sweden's Sweden-
-But the country has begun to scratch from the chaos in the early 18th century.
Sweden has a popular form of government, a dawn democracy
-And has not been fought for a long time.
Surely that is the top?
No, the hats dream of revenge in Russia.
The lead leader Arvid Horn is dismissed, and Sweden is attacking Russia.
Now the country will be restored, but it will be a real failure.
The war lasts for two years, Sweden wins nothing, and Russia takes Finland.
To get it back, Sweden must agree on concessions.
At this time, Ulrika Eleonora has died childless.
Sweden had no follower.
The Russian Empress said that if one chose her relative Adolf Fredrik-
-Ad it improve the terms of peace.
Russia wants an ally on the throne.
It annoys the valley farmers.
They start carpentry together things that are not only used for agriculture.
Here we have a nail club - a fairly simple weapon.
-And Russia's involvement in the choice of throne followers.
They train all the way to Stockholm.
But it will mostly be a tumult
-White ends with dead fellows and over 3,000 captured rebellioners.
When Fredrik dies, Adolf takes over Fredrik the throne, to the dismay of the Dalkarls.
The king's wife is called Lovisa Ulrika.
That she was something to count on synthesis early.
Here is a small gold box.
If you open it, you can see an object that looks like a weight paper.
Previously, it was considered a sign of future happiness.
It was thought that the princess could carry this as a bracelet.
Sweden's "Power Couple" is not satisfied with its back position.
In order to strengthen their power, they decide to implement a coup d'état.
The coup attempt was not well thought out.
The king gets sick, and the whole thing is revealed early.
They arrest the insurgents, and they are executed before the eyes of the royal couple.
Lovisa Ulrika's foster membrane did not work as a happiness amulet at that time.
Sweden is at the forefront when it comes to art, culture and science.
His father and Fredrik I came to Sweden as adults.
Gustav III tries to create order in the Swedish Parliament-
-But now the election fraud beats the ceiling.
In the election 1771, then we arrive at the last parliamentary period of freedom
-Had it was hard to agree on who would be allowed to vote in the presidential election.
In the bourgeoisie, this speech valet-
-So pass that there was a blood white.
They were struck at the ballot box about who would stop in banknotes and not.
Corruption, electoral fraud and fights inside the Riksdag.
In this chaos, Gustav III sees an opportunity to take back power.
He plans a coup d'état, and he doesn't get sick as his father.
The coup is also better planned.
In August 1772 he succeeds with the help of officers locking in government-
-And force them to agree to a new form of government that gives the king power.
Gustav III's coup effectively ends the time of freedom.
We are back where we started, with a strong royal power and a weak parliament.
You have seen in different ways in freedom.
It is either the freest period Sweden had.
Others say this was the most corrupt time in Swedish history.
To choose this compromise, peace-loving Arvid Horn-
— on the stamp
-Is both to point out that we should be able to agree in the country-
-But also to go back to the fact that we have been part of Sweden.
We may be able to get support in Sweden if Russia will attack us.
Which they do three years later.
Although Gustav III turns back very-
-There is something that is gaining momentum that exists today - democracy.
Even though few were allowed to vote, that the election fraud has never been so great-